Azerbaijan! Azerbaijan!
Oh you glorious Fatherland of the brave child!
We are all together ready to give our lives for you!
We are all together strong to sacrifice our blood for you!
Live blessed with your three-coloured flag!
Thousands of lives were sacrificed,
Your chest became an arena for battles!
Soldiers gave their life for you,
All of them became heroes!
You shall be a garden full of roses
The sacrifice of our souls anytime for you!
Never–ending love for you
Have got a place in my heart!
In order to maintain your honor,
In order to elevate your flag,
The young are intended sententiously!
The glorious Homeland,
Azerbaijan!